[{"answer": "Yes, I think you're right.", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 35, "question": "And the motivation appears to be financial, is that right?", "qSentId": 34}, {"answer": "Well, I know, you know, how it was down there because I was there quite a bit.", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 44, "question": "Can you tell me what your reaction is to this shocking story?", "qSentId": 43}, {"answer": "Yes, that's wrong.", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 49, "question": "So when you say lies, I mean -- when you say lies, are you disputing that your son along with the other suspects kept this woman who is, we know, mentally disabled and her child captive for two years?", "qSentId": 48}, {"answer": "What is -- everything is wrong about it.", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 54, "question": "What is wrong about it?", "qSentId": 53}, {"answer": "Absolutely none of this is true, no.", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "So are you saying that absolutely none of this is true?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "No, after you.", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 64, "question": "Excuse me?", "qSentId": 63}, {"answer": "No, you say what you want to say, Becky.", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 66, "question": "What was that?", "qSentId": 65}, {"answer": "Because Jordie and Jessie heard the little girl crying a lot in the bedroom that they were at.", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 69, "question": "If none of this happened, why are the police taking this dramatic action of charging your son and his partner and the third person and potentially a fourth with extremely serious offenses?", "qSentId": 68}, {"answer": "She was giving them a couple of hundred dollars a month for staying there and she was getting her own food.", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 76, "question": "ORGAN: Who was taking her money that she was getting for her disability?", "qSentId": 75}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 81, "question": "Have you spoken to your son Jordie about this since he was charged?", "qSentId": 80}, {"answer": "He's devastated that all this is being said about them.", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 83, "question": "And what does he say?", "qSentId": 82}, {"answer": "Yes, yes, I have.", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 92, "question": "You say that you -- you have had this woman and her daughter at your house in the last two years several times, is that right?", "qSentId": 91}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 94, "question": "And she gave no suggestion to you that she was being held captive or being abused in any way?", "qSentId": 93}, {"answer": "Yes, I do.", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 97, "question": "Did you have any way of -- did you have any way of proving that she was at your house?", "qSentId": 96}, {"answer": "I've got plenty of pictures proving it.", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 99, "question": "How would you prove it?", "qSentId": 98}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 101, "question": "Of this woman in the last two years inside your property?", "qSentId": 100}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 103, "question": "So you believe that your son and the other suspects who have been charged are being framed and that this woman herself has been guilty of abusing her child, is that your position?", "qSentId": 102}, {"answer": "Well, you know, this is a little town of Ashland, and they do know Jordie and they know Jess and they are just trying to make a big case out of what Shannon did.", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 106, "question": "It doesn't make much sense to me that the police would simply believe her word against three other people if, as you say, there has been absolutely no abuse whatsoever?", "qSentId": 105}, {"answer": "No, because we knew that there wouldn't be an issue, you know, especially and particularly here in southern West Virginia where we're primarily -- I mean, basically we are a gun culture here.", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 129, "question": "Did you at any point think that this T-shirt would breech any of the school's regulations?", "qSentId": 128}, {"answer": "Well, you may have an argument there in certain places, Piers.", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 195, "question": "Would it not be best to have the debate about gun control and guns and the NRA out of school classrooms and school playgrounds?", "qSentId": 194}, {"answer": "I think it was irreversible and significant damage to this nation.", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 217, "question": "How damaging is this to the national security of the American people that this trust was violated?", "qSentId": 216}, {"answer": "I believe it has, and I believe it will hurt us and our allies.", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 219, "question": "Has this helped America's enemies?", "qSentId": 218}, {"answer": "This is what the government says in every single case whenever somebody exposes what they want to hide from the people over whom they're ruling.", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 230, "question": "What is your reaction to that?", "qSentId": 229}, {"answer": "No, it's not that they are lying.", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 238, "question": "So when they say that more than 50 plots globally have been thwarted as a direct result of all this surveillance, are they lying?", "qSentId": 237}, {"answer": "Look, I had clearances for communications intelligence for years in the government.", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 249, "question": "Because I think the key question now is what is the line and who draws it?", "qSentId": 248}, {"answer": "They were dropped because the president was, among other things, conducting warrantless wiretapping on which I was overheard and lying about it, by the way.", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 275, "question": "You weren't -- but the charges were dropped, right?", "qSentId": 274}, {"answer": "No, I think - first, I think he's benefited very much -- he's benefited.", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 283, "question": "Should Edward Snowden have stayed in America?", "qSentId": 282}, {"answer": "I mean, it's --", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "What is your reaction to his tragic death?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "Unspeakably horrible.", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 325, "question": "Are you speaking to me?", "qSentId": 324}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 361, "question": "Do you think we could find a way in?", "qSentId": 360}, {"answer": "Good.", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 371, "question": "Paris, how the devil are you?", "qSentId": 370}, {"answer": "Definitely, because, you know, this could not have happened, you know, five or 10 years ago.", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 387, "question": "Has that to make you change the way you behave on Twitter and so on?", "qSentId": 386}, {"answer": "Yes, they actually tried to take my dog, which --", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 390, "question": "They tried to take your dog, didn't they?", "qSentId": 389}, {"answer": "I love Sofia.", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 402, "question": "How did you find her?", "qSentId": 401}, {"answer": "All my fragrances are over $1.5 billion so far.", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "Can you horrify my viewers now and tell them how much the last fragrance 16th, Dazzle, how much it took in sales?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 425, "question": "And you're not married yet, are you?", "qSentId": 424}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 430, "question": "Do you, Piers Morgan, take Paris Hilton to be your wedded wife?", "qSentId": 429}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 432, "question": "And do you, Paris Hilton, take Piers Morgan to be your lawful wedded husband?", "qSentId": 431}, {"answer": "I call him my man.", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 448, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 447}, {"answer": "Yes, he's very mature.", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 450, "question": "Is he a man yet?", "qSentId": 449}, {"answer": "He's very aware of that.", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 452, "question": "Is he aware that I exist as your only husband to date?", "qSentId": 451}, {"answer": "Of course, he's a little bit jealous of you.", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 454, "question": "How is he dealing of that?", "qSentId": 453}, {"answer": "You know, we just celebrated our one-year anniversary and I've never been happier.", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 457, "question": "Do you think you may see any wedding bells with River?", "qSentId": 456}, {"answer": "Well, you know, that's bad news for him.", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "What the hell is going on?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "Look, I mean, the minute that you are mentioning in the same sentence as Dick Cheney when your campaign slogan was hope and change, I think you're in a very problematic position and you mentioned the word trust, and I think that that is the one word that describes where he is right now.", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 512, "question": "All this stuff recently just seems to be nibbling away at the fact that he was Mr. Transparent and now he's Mr. Sneaky?", "qSentId": 511}, {"answer": "I don't think so.", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 522, "question": "Is he losing the people that really, really put the money up and backed him?", "qSentId": 521}, {"answer": "We're not spied on but their conversations are --", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 532, "question": "But isn't this the point?", "qSentId": 531}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "Isn't that the difference?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "Brand.", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 547, "question": "Brand experience?", "qSentId": 546}, {"answer": "Piers --", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 564, "question": "I mean, they went as if they couldn't understand a word he was saying?", "qSentId": 563}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know.", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 584, "question": "Why would she use that analogy, do you think?", "qSentId": 583}, {"answer": "I love Russell Brand.", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 597, "question": "Would Rasputin divorce his wife by text?", "qSentId": 596}, {"answer": "Well, I can't imagine -- people do a lot of stuff by text messaging.", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 611, "question": "Van Jones, I mean, can you ever imagine being in the position where you would divorce somebody by text message?", "qSentId": 610}, {"answer": "There -- I mean, there are -- you know, it's interesting that technological advancements have done so many great things, but I think we've lost the intimacy of having these sorts of conversations and it allows people, especially young people, to have an excuse to not talk about awkward things that can be very uncomfortable like this, like a divorce.", "docId": "130618pmt", "aSentId": 617, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 616}]